Guide to the University of Chicago Department of Buildings and Grounds Records 1892-1965
University of Chicago Library
Office of the President. Records
Ernest DeWitt Burton. Papers
Thomas W. Goodspeed. Papers
Edgar Goodspeed. Papers
Marion Talbot. Papers
Harold Swift. Papers
Archival Buildings Files
Subject Headings
Flook, Lyman R.; University of Chicago -- History; University of Chicago. Dept. of Buildings and Grounds; University of Chicago -- Buildings; Architecture -- Illinois -- Chicago -- History; Building -- Illinois -- Chicago -- History; College buildings -- Illinois -- Chicago
INVENTORY
- Series I: Department of Building and Grounds, 1892-1932
  - Subseries 1: General Office Files
    - Architectural records of the University, correspondence concerning, 1926-1930 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Architectural references (miscellaneous correspondence and publications) (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Budgets; 1927-1928, 1928-1929 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Buildings demolished or moved, 1924-1931 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Buildings planned but not built, 1919-1931 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Buildings under construction, financial statements, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Buildings under construction, financial statements, Jan-June 1926 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Buildings under construction, financial statements, Jul-Dec 1926 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Buildings under construction, financial statements, Feb-June 1927 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Buildings under construction, financial statements, Aug-Dec 1927 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Buildings under construction, financial statements, Jan-June 1928 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Buildings under construction, financial statements, Aug-Dec 1928 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Buildings under construction, financial statements, Jan-June 1929 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Buildings under construction, financial statements, Jul-Dec 1929 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Buildings under construction, financial statements, Jan-June 1930 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Buildings under construction, financial statements, Jul-Dec 1930 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Buildings under construction, financial statements, Jan-June 1931 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Buildings under construction, financial statements, Jul-Dec 1931 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Buildings under construction, financial statements, Jan-June 1932 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Buildings under construction, financial statements, Jul-Dec 1932 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Buildings under construction, financial statements, Jan-May 1933 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Buildings under construction, financial statements, Jan-June 1934 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - City of Chicago fire inspections; 1916, 1917, 1922, 1925 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Contractors and trades, Lists, 1927, 1928 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Construction summaries, annual; 1927, 1928, 1931, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Cost and cubage tabulations, comparative, 1924-1931 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Flook, Lyman R., personal (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Flook, Lyman R., personal (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Flook, Lyman R., personal (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Insurance inspections; 1913, 1920 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Landis Award Committee, publications (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Office organization, 1919-1931 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Other campuses (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Power needs (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Price book, Mar 1929-Jul 1931 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Sixty-first Street shops (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Water systems (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 2: Landscaping and Maintenance
    - Hull Court (Olmsted Bros., 1903), specifications (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Walks, drives, drainage (Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge, 1906-1912), specifications (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Walks, paving, sodding (Coolidge and Hodgdon, 1915), specifications (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Quadrangles landscaping (Bennett, Parsons and Frost, 1926-1930), correspondence (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Chicago Lying-in Hospital landscaping (Thomas Seyster, 1930), specifications and correspondence (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - International House and other landscaping (Beatrix Farrand, 1920), correspondence and financial statements (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Landscape maintenance, 1924-1931 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 3: Individual Buildings
    - Anatomy Building, SEE Hull Biological Laboratories, Beecher Hall (H. I. Cobb, 1899), Alterations, 1899-1900; specifications and correspondence (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Beecher Hall, Specifications, Billings Hospital, SEE Medical Group Biology Center, SEE Hull Biological Laboratories (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Blackstone Avenue Power Plant (John J. Davey, 1929; Philip Maher, Consulting), Specifications, general (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Blackstone Avenue Power Plant, Specifications, A.C. distribution (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Blackstone Avenue Power Plant, Specifications, boilers (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Blackstone Avenue Power Plant, Specifications, caissons, general excavation (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Blackstone Avenue Power Plant, Specifications, chimneys, coal handling (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Blackstone Avenue Power Plant, Specifications, forced draft fans (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Blackstone Avenue Power Plant, Specifications, piping, pre-heaters (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Blackstone Avenue Power Plant, Specifications, structured steel, super-heaters (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Blackstone Avenue Power Plant, Specifications, tunnels (Box 7, Folder 2-4)
    - Blackstone Avenue Power Plant, Specifications, water heater and softener (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Blackstone Avenue Power Plant, Specifications, wiring (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Blackstone Avenue Power Plant, Planning, 1923-1927 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Blackstone Avenue Power Plant, Planning, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Blackstone Avenue Power Plant, Planning, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Blackstone Avenue Power Plant, Planning, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Blackstone Avenue Power Plant, Operation (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Blackstone Avenue Power Plant, Progress reports, 1927-1930 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Blackstone Avenue Power Plant, Symbolism and ornamentation (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Blackstone Avenue Power Plant, Costs and audits (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Blaine Hall (James Gamble Rogers, 1903), Specifications, furniture (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Bobs Roberts Hospital (Coolidge and Hodgdon, 1930), Specifications, general (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Bobs Roberts Hospital, Specifications, mechanical (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Bobs Roberts Hospital, Specifications, fixtures and equipment (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Bobs Roberts Hospital, Planning, 1927-1930 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Bobs Roberts Hospital, Progress reports, 1929-1930 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Bobs Roberts Hospital, Interior furnishings and equipment (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Bobs Roberts Hospital, Symbolism, mural, portrait (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Bobs Roberts Hospital, Costs, Bond Chapel, SEE Theology Group Botany Building, SEE Hull Biological Laboratories (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Botany Laboratory, Greenhouses, and Potting Shed (Perkins, Chatten and Hammond, 1930), Specifications, laboratory (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Botany Laboratory, Greenhouses, and Potting Shed, Specifications, greenhouses and potting shed (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Botany Laboratory, Greenhouses, and Potting Shed, Planning, 1924-1930 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Botany Laboratory, Greenhouses, and Potting Shed, Interior furnishing and equipment (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Botany Laboratory, Greenhouses, and Potting Shed, Symbolism (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Botany Laboratory, Greenhouses, and Potting Shed, Greenhouses (Lord and Burnham) (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Botany Laboratory, Greenhouses, and Potting Shed, Costs, audits (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Burton-Judson Courts (Zantzinger, Borie and Medary, 1931), specifications, general (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Burton-Judson Courts, Specifications, heating, plumbing, ventilation (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Burton-Judson Courts, Specifications, kitchen equipment, refrigeration (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Burton-Judson Courts, Planning, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Burton-Judson Courts, Planning, 1929 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Burton-Judson Courts, Planning, 1930-1931 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Burton-Judson Courts, Progress reports (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Burton-Judson Courts, Interior furnishing and equipment (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Burton-Judson Courts, Sculpture, woodcarving, ornamental iron, stained glass (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Burton-Judson Courts, Costs, audit (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Business East, formerly Law School (Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge, 1904), Specifications, general (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Business East, Specifications, furniture and lighting (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Business East, Alterations contract, 1909; alterations specifications, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Chicago Lying-in Hospital (Schmidt, Garden and Erikson, 1931), Specifications, general (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Chicago Lying-in Hospital, Specifications, mechanical (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Chicago Lying-in Hospital, Planning, 1927-1931 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Chicago Lying-in Hospital, Interior furnishing and equipment (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Chicago Lying-in Hospital, Symbolism (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Chicago Lying-in Hospital, Costs, audit (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Classics Building (Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge, 1914), Specifications, general (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Classics Building, Specifications, mechanical (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Classics Building, Specifications, cut stone (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Cobb Hall (H. I. Cobb, 1892), Specifications, heating and ventilation (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Cobb Hall, Alteration specifications, 1907, Culver Hall, SEE Hull Biological Laboratories (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Eckhart Hall (Charles Z. Klauder, 1929), Specifications, general (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Eckhart Hall, Specifications, mechanical (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Eckhart Hall, Planning, 1927-1928 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Eckhart Hall, Planning, 1929-1930 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Eckhart Hall, Progress reports, 1929 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Eckhart Hall, Progress reports, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Eckhart Hall, Interior furnishing and equipment (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Eckhart Hall, Symbolism, carving, inscriptions, portraits (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Eckhart Hall, Costs, audit (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Field House (Holabird and Root, 1932), Specifications, general, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Field House, Specifications, general, 1931 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Field House, Specifications, mechanical (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Field House, Planning, 1924-1928 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Field House, Planning, 1929-1932 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Field House, Progress reports, 1931-1932 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Field House, Costs, audit (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Foster Hall (H. I. Cobb, 1893) specifications, heating and ventilation (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Foster Hall, Refurbishing, correspondence, 1926-1927 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Gates Hall (H. I. Cobb, 1892), Alterations (Coolidge and Hodgdon, 1923), specifications (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Goodspeed Hall (H. I. Cobb, 1892), Remodeling (Julius Floto,1937); specifications, general (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Goodspeed Hall, Remodeling, specifications, mechanical (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Green Hall (H. I. Cobb, 1899), Specifications, general (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Harper Memorial Library (Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge, 1912) Specifications, general (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Harper Memorial Library, Specifications, mechanical (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Harper Memorial Library, Alterations (Coolidge and Hodgdon, 1926), correspondence (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Harper Memorial Library, Burton window, 1927; Harper bas-relief, 1932 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Haskell Hall (H. I. Cobb, 1896), Specifications, carpenter work (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Hicks-McElwee Orthopedics Hospital (Coolidge and Hodgdon, 1931), Specifications, general (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Hicks-McElwee Orthopedics Hospital, Specifications, mechanical (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Hicks-McElwee Orthopedics Hospital, Specifications, equipment (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Hicks-McElwee Orthopedics Hospital, Planning, 1927-1930 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Hicks-McElwee Orthopedics Hospital, Progress schedule (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Hicks-McElwee Orthopedics Hospital, Interior furnishing and equipment (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Hicks-McElwee Orthopedics Hospital, Symbolism, cornerstone (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Hicks-McElwee Orthopedics Hospital, Costs, audit (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Hitchcock Hall (Dwight H. Perkins, 1902), Alterations (1913), specifications (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Hull Biological Laboratories, Culver, Anatomy, Zoology, Biology (H. I. Cobb, 1897), Specifications, masonry and marble (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Hull Biological Laboratories, Specifications, mechanical (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Hull Biological Laboratories, Anatomy Building alterations and additions (Holabird and Roche, 1922), specifications, Hutchinson Commons, SEE Tower Group (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - International House (Holabird and Root, 1932), Specifications, general (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - International House, Specifications, mechanical (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - International House, Specifications, kitchen equipment, hardware (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - International House, Planning, 1929-1931 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - International House, Progress reports, 1931-1932 (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
    - International House, Interior furnishing and equipment (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - International House, Symbolism, carving, fountain (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - International House, Costs (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - International House, Audits (Box 21, Folder 6-7)
    - Jones Laboratory (Coolidge and Hodgdon, 1929) Specifications, general (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Jones Laboratory, Specifications, mechanical (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Jones Laboratory, Specifications, equipment (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Jones Laboratory, Planning, 1926-1929 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Jones Laboratory, Progress reports, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Jones Laboratory, Schlesinger, H. I., correspondence, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Jones Laboratory, Interior furnishing and equipment (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Jones Laboratory, Symbolism and ornamentation (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Jones Laboratory, Costs (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Judd Hall (Armstrong, Furst and Tilton, 1931) Specifications, general (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Judd Hall, Planning, 1923-1931 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Judd Hall, Progress reports, 1930-1931 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Judd Hall, Audits (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Kelly Hall (H. I. Cobb, 1893) Alterations (Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge, 1906), specifications (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Kent Chemical Laboratory (H. I. Cobb, 1894) Specifications, mechanical (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Kent Chemical Laboratory, Alterations (Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge, 1909), specifications, Law School, SEE Business East Mand Hall, SEE Tower Group (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Medical Group (Coolidge and Hodgdon, 1925-1928) Specifications, general (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Medical Group, Specifications, mechanical (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Medical Group, Specifications, equipment (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Medical Group, Planning, 1920-1928 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Medical Group, Interior furnishings and equipment (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Medical Group, Tablets and inscriptions (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Medical Group, Costs, Mitchell Tower, SEE Tower Group (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Morgan Park Academy, Park Hall alterations and additions (H. I. Cobb, 1896), specifications (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Morgan Park Academy, Gymnasium (Dwight H. Perkins, 1900), specifications (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Ida Noyes Hall (Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge, 1916), Specifications, general (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Ida Noyes Hall, Specifications, mechanical (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Ida Noyes Hall, Donor (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Ida Noyes Hall, Planning (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Ida Noyes Hall, Dedication (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Ida Noyes Hall, Inventories and correspondence, furnishings, 1915-1938 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Ida Noyes Hall, oriental rugs, 1916-1956 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Ida Noyes Hall, art objects, 1920-1938 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Ida Noyes Hall, Mural (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Ida Noyes Hall, Use, policy for, 1916-1921; in relation to women’s dormitories. 1931 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Ida Noyes Hall, Guides, brochures, biography of Ida Noyes (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Oriental Institute (Mayer, Murray and Phillip, 1931) Specifications, general (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Oriental Institute, Specifications, mechanical (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Oriental Institute, Planning, 1928-1931 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Oriental Institute, Progress reports, 1930-1931 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Oriental Institute, Interior furnishings and equipment (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Oriental Institute, Symbolism, carving, tablet (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Oriental Institute, Audits (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Orthogenic School (Coolidge and Hodgdon, 1917), Additions and alterations (Edward F. Jansson, 1930), specifications (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - President’s House (H. I. Cobb, 1895), Specifications, general (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - President’s House, Alterations and additions (Coolidge and Hodgdon, 1929), specifications (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Press Building (Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge, 1902), Specifications, general (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Press Building, Specifications, mechanical (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Press Building, Specifications, alterations (1902, 1907); addition (1929) (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Quadrangle Club (Howard V. D. Shaw, 1921), Specifications, general (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Heating contract, 1922, Reynolds Club SEE Tower Group (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Ricketts Laboratory (Holabird and Roche, 1914), Specifications, general (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Ricketts Laboratory South (Henry K. Holsman, 1922), Specifications, general (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller Chapel (Bertram G. Goodhue, Goodhue Associates, 1928), Specifications, general (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller Chapel, Specifications, mechanical (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Rockefeller Chapel, Planning, 1918 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Rockefeller Chapel, Planning, 1919 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Rockefeller Chapel, Planning, 1920 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Rockefeller Chapel, Planning, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Rockefeller Chapel, Planning, 1924 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Rockefeller Chapel, Planning, 1925-1926 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Chapel, Progress reports, 1925 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Chapel, Progress reports, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Chapel, Progress reports, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Chapel, Progress reports, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller Chapel, Progress reports, 1928 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller Chapel, Acoustics (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller Chapel, Architects’ correspondence (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller Chapel, Carillon (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Rockefeller Chapel, Goodspeed, Edgar; correspondence and The University Chapel (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Rockefeller Chapel, Indiana Limestone Co., correspondence and publications (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Rockefeller Chapel, Interior furnishing and equipment (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Rockefeller Chapel, Organ (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Rockefeller Chapel, Symbolism, carving, models (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Chapel, Tablets, inscriptions (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Chapel, Windows (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Chapel, University of Chicago Magazine, Dec 1928; building trades advertisements featuring the Chapel (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Rosenwald Hall (Holabird and Roche, 1914), Specifications, general (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Rosenwald Hall, Specifications, mechanical (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Ryerson Physical Laboratory (H. I. Cobb, 1893), Specifications, mechanical (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Ryerson Physical Laboratory, Specifications, additions and alterations (Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge, 1910) (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Ryerson Physical Laboratory, Specifications, additions and alterations (Coolidge and Hodgdon, 1927-1929) (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Snell Hall (H. I. Cobb, 1893), Specifications, mechanical (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Social Science Research Building (Coolidge and Hodgdon, 1929), Specifications, general (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
    - Social Science Research Building, Specifications, mechanical (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Social Science Research Building, Planning, 1926-1927 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Social Science Research Building, Planning, 1928 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Social Science Research Building, Progress reports, 1929 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Social Science Research Building, Interior furnishing and equipment (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Social Science Research Building, Symbolism, models, carving, tablet (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Social Science Research Building, Costs, audits (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Stagg Field (Holabird and Root, 1929), Specifications, general (James Gamble Rogers, 1903) (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Stagg Field, Specifications, alterations and additions (Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge, 1914) (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Stagg Field, Specifications, tunnel and piping (1914) (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Stagg Field, Specifications, general (Holabird and Roche, 1926) (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Stagg Field, Planning, 1923-1929 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Sunny Gymnasium (Armstrong, Furst and Tilton, 1929), Specifications, general (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Sunny Gymnasium, Specifications mechanical (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Sunny Gymnasium, Planning, 1927-1929 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Sunny Gymnasium, Architects’ correspondence, 1928 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Sunny Gymnasium, Architects’ correspondence, 1929 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Sunny Gymnasium, Architects’ correspondence, 1929 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Sunny Gymnasium, Fence, Jackman Field (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Sunny Gymnasium, Interior furnishing and equipment (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Sunny Gymnasium, Symbolism, carving (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Sunny Gymnasium, Costs, Swift Hall, SEE Theology Group (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Theology Group, Bond Chapel, Cloister, Swift Hall (Coolidge and Hodgdon, 1926), Specifications, general (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Theology Group, Specifications, mechanical (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Theology Group, Planning, 1924-1926 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Bond Chapel; specifications, general (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Bond Chapel; mechanical (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Bond Chapel; inferior furnishing and equipment, organ, inscriptions (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Bond Chapel; costs (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Cloister; specifications (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Cloister; planning, 1925-1928 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Swift Hall; planning, 1924-1927 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Swift Hall; progress reports, 1924-1925 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Swift Hall; interior furnishing and equipment (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Swift Hall; models, inscriptions (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Swift Hall; costs (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Tower Group, Mandel Hall, Hutchinson Commons, Reynolds Club, Mitchell Tower (Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge, 1903), Specifications, superstructure (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Tower Group, Specifications, foundations (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Tower Group, Hutchinson Commons; specifications, furniture and fittings (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Tower Group, Hutchinson Commons; specifications, kitchen (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Tower Group, Hutchinson Commons; specifications, mechanical (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Tower Group, Hutchinson Commons; specifications, spa and private dining room (1923) (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Tower Group, Mandel Hall; curtain and scenery, 1903 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Tower Group, Mandel Hall; alterations (Coolidge and Hodgdon, 1926-1929), specifications and correspondence (Box 33, Folder 8)